Finding Aid for League of Women Voters of Michigan Records 1926-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Local leagues
  - Local chapter records
    - Kalamazoo
      - Non-partisan policy 1964, 1970 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Lansing
      - By-laws 1946, 1947, 1957, 1959, 1963 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1948-1979, 4 folders (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1947-1974 (Box 19)
      - Non-partisan policy 1966, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Voters guides 1970 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Lapeer (defunct)
      - By-laws 1954 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1952-1961 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1952-1961 (Box 19)
      - Membership lists 1951-1962 (Box 19)
      - Minutes 1961 (Box 19)
      - Voters service reports 1954 (Box 19)
      - Newspaper clippings 1954, 1961 (Box 19)
    - Livonia
      - By-laws 1960, 1962 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1961-1974, 4 folders (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1956-1962 (Box 19)
      - Minutes 1960, 1967 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Ludington (defunct)
      - Annual reports undated, 1950-1951 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1950-1951 (Box 19)
      - Minutes undated, 1950 (Box 19)
      - Membership and leadership undated, 1951 (Box 19)
      - Budget undated, 1951-1952 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Manistee
      - By-laws 1965 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1965-1974, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1964-1973 (Box 19)
      - Voters guides 1970 (Box 19)
    - Marquette
      - By-laws undated, 1952 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1953-1974, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1948-1970 (Box 19)
      - Minutes undated, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Voters service 1954 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Menominee (defunct)
      - By-laws 1954 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1952-1954 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1950-1955 (Box 19)
      - Minutes undated, 1952-1955 (Box 19)
      - Membership and leadership undated, 1952-1954 (Box 19)
      - Budget undated, 1952-1955 (Box 19)
      - Newspaper clippings 1951-1953 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Midland
      - By-laws undated (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1966-1978, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1956-1968 (Box 19)
      - Voters guide 1970 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Monroe
      - By-laws undated (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1960-1964 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence 1960-1963 (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea (Box 19)
    - Mount Clemens
      - By-laws 1953 (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1947-1959, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Annual reports 1960-1972, 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box 20)
      - Voters service report 1954 (Box 20)
      - Voters guide 1970 (Box 20)
      - Miscellanea (Box 20)
    - Mount Pleasant
      - Annual reports undated, 1969-1974, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Correspondence 1952-1971 (Box 20)
      - Voters guide 1969, 1972 (Box 20)
      - Information guide 1969, 1971 (Box 20)
    - Muskegon
      - By-laws undated (Box 20)
      - Annual reports
        - 1947-1953 (Box 20)
        - 1971-1978 (Box 20)
      - Correspondence 1948-1972 (Box 20)
      - Miscellanea (Box 20)
    - New Buffalo
      - Correspondence 1969-1971 (Box 20)
    - Niles
      - Annual reports 1957-1976, 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Correspondence 1956-1977 (Box 20)
      - Voters guide 1968, 1970 (Box 20)
      - Miscellanea (Box 20)
    - Northville-Plymouth-Canton-Novi
      - By-laws 1966, 1970, 1973 (Box 20)
      - Annual reports 1969-1974, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Annual meeting 1970-1991 (Box 20)
      - Bulletins 1974-1976 (Box 20)
      - Newsletter: Area Voter (later Voter) 1982-1992 (Box 20)
      - Handbook 1981 (Box 20)
      - Correspondence 1964-1975 (Box 20)
      - Voters guides 1970 (Box 20)
      - Miscellanea (Box 20)
      - Minutes 1969-1989, 18 folders (Box 32)
      - Subject files (unlisted) (Box 32)
      - Videotape (Box 32)
      - Scrapbooks 1968-1981, 3 volumes (Box 33)
    - Oak Park-Huntington Woods
      - By-laws undated, 1955, 1961 (Box 34)
      - Annual reports 1956-1970, 3 folders (Box 34)
      - Correspondence 1956-1969 (Box 34)
      - Newspaper clippings 1959-1961 (Box 34)
      - Miscellanea (Box 34)
    - Oakland County League
      - Correspondence 1951-1967 (Box 34)
      - Statement of Policy 1952-1966 (Box 34)
      - Minutes 1953-1967 (Box 34)
      - Reports 1955, 1968 (Box 34)
      - Voters guides 1956, 1970 (Box 34)
    - Owosso (defunct)
      - By-laws 1956, 1957, 1960, and 1963 (Box 34)
      - Annual reports 1956-1963, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Correspondence 1955-1963 (Box 34)
      - Membership undated, 1960-1963 (Box 34)
      - Minutes 1956 (Box 34)
      - Financial papers 1956-1963 (Box 34)
      - Newspaper clippings, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Miscellanea (Box 34)
    - Plymouth (defunct)
      (later consolidated into Northville-Plymouth)
      - Correspondence 1941-1945 (Box 34)
      - Membership undated (Box 34)
      - Minutes 1945 (Box 34)
    - Pontiac (defunct)
      - By-laws undated, 1967 (Box 34)
      - Annual reports 1950-1968, 4 folders (Box 34)
      - Correspondence 1950-1968 (Box 34)
      - Minutes 1966-1967 (Box 34)
      - Membership undated, 1950-1951, 1967 (Box 34)
      - Newsletters 1953, 1966-1967 (Box 34)
      - Financial information 1949-1950, 1968 (Box 34)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 34)
      - Voters service report 1951, 1954 (Box 34)
      - Miscellanea (Box 34)
    - Port Huron
      - By-laws 1947, 1961 (Box 34)
      - Annual reports 1947-1974, 5 folders (Box 34)
      - Correspondence 1952-1977 (Box 34)
      - Voters service 1954 (Box 34)
      - Newspaper clippings undated, 1950-1952 (Box 34)
      - Miscellanea (Box 34)
    - Powers (defunct)
      - Annual reports 1952-1955 (Box 34)
      - Correspondence 1952-1956 (Box 34)
      - Minutes 1952-1955 (Box 34)
      - Membership 1952-1955 (Box 34)
      - Financial information 1952-1955 (Box 34)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 34)
      - Miscellanea (Box 34)
    - Rochester
      - By-laws undated, 1959, 1962, 1964 (Box 21)
      - Annual reports 1961-1974, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Correspondence 1959-1967 (Box 21)
      - Non-partisan policy 1963, 1965, 1969 (Box 21)
      - Voters guides 1970 (Box 21)
      - Miscellanea (Box 21)
    - Royal Oak
      - By-laws undated, 1949, 1957 (Box 21)
      - Annual reports 1947-1978, 5 folders (Box 21)
      - Correspondence 1947-1958 (Box 21)
      - Minutes 1968-1969 (Box 21)
      - Non-partisan policy 1967 (Box 21)
      - Voter survey 1954 (Box 21)
      - Voters guides 1970-1971 (Box 21)
      - Newspaper clippings 1954-1964 (Box 21)
      - Miscellanea (Box 21)
    - Saginaw
      - By-laws 1947, 1949, 1951, 1966 (Box 21)
      - Annual reports 1947-1974, 5 folders (Box 21)
      - Correspondence 1948-1978 (Box 21)
      - Minutes 1953 (Box 21)
      - Voters service 1954 (Box 21)
      - Newspaper clippings 1948-1962 (Box 21)
      - Miscellanea (Box 21)
    - Sault Sainte Marie
      - By-laws 1960 (Box 21)
      - Annual report 1965-1974, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Correspondence 1950-1977, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Voters guides 1971 (Box 21)
      - Newspaper clippings 1966 (Box 21)
    - Southeast Oakland area
      - Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box 21)
      - Minutes 1971-1973 (Box 21)
      - Reports 1969 (Box 21)
      - Newsletter 1973 (Box 21)
      - Miscellanea (Box 21)
    - Southeast Oakland County (defunct)
      - By-laws 1971 (Box 21)
      - Annual reports 1970-1974 (Box 21)
      - Correspondence 1969-1973 (Box 21)
      - Membership 1972 (Box 21)
      - Minutes 1972 (Box 21)
      - Voters guides undated, 1966-1970 (Box 21)
      - Formation of County Council 1950-1953, 1964 (Box 21)
      - Newspaper clippings 1972 (Box 21)
    - Southfield-Lathrup, Village
      - By-laws 1967 (Box 21)
      - Annual reports 1960-1974, 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Correspondence 1962-1969 (Box 21)
      - Voters guides 1970, 1972 (Box 22)
      - Newspaper clippings 1964 (Box 22)
      - Miscellanea (Box 22)
    - Trenton
      - By-laws 1952, 1955 (Box 22)
      - Annual reports 1952-1954, 1957-1961 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence 1951-1953 (Box 22)
      - Voters service 1954 (Box 22)
      - Newspaper clippings 1956 (Box 22)
      - Miscellanea (Box 22)
    - Troy
      - Annual reports 1974 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence 1974 (Box 22)
    - Warren-Sterling Heights
      - By-laws undated (Box 22)
      - Annual reports 1962-1976, 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Correspondence 1962-1968 (Box 22)
      - Minutes 1978 (Box 22)
      - Voters guides 1964, 1970 (Box 22)
      - Newspaper clippings 1964 (Box 22)
      - Miscellanea (Box 22)
      - 2001 accession: bylaws, minutes, correspondence, issue files (Box 22)
      - 2001 accession: bylaws, minutes, correspondence, issue files (Box 35)
      - 2001 accession: bylaws, minutes, correspondence, issue files (Box 23)
    - Wayne (defunct)
      - By-laws undated, 1953, 1956 (Box 23)
      - Annual reports 1951-1965, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Correspondence 1952-1965 (Box 23)
      - Minutes 1952, 1959-1960 (Box 23)
      - Membership 1953 (Box 23)
      - Newsletter 1965 (Box 23)
      - Newspaper clippings undated, 1956 (Box 23)
      - Miscellanea (Box 23)
    - Wayne County Council
      - Agreement 1952-1954 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence 1952-1961 (Box 23)
      - Minutes 1956-1969 (Box 23)
      - Voters guides 1956, 1966 (Box 23)
    - West Bloomfield-Farmington
      - By-laws 1953, 1957, 1967, 1969 (Box 23)
      - Annual reports 1947-1974, 5 folders (Box 23)
      - Correspondence 1951-1969 (Box 23)
      - Voters guides 1970 (Box 23)
      - Miscellanea (Box 23)
    - West Oakland County
      - Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 23)
      - Reports 1973-1974 (Box 23)
      - Miscellanea (Box 23)
    - Ypsilanti
      - By-laws 1965 (Box 23)
      - Annual reports 1957-1974, 4 folders (Box 23)
      - Correspondence 1957-1974 (Box 23)
      - Minutes 1959, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
      - Non-partisan policy 1961, 1965 (Box 23)
      - Newspaper clippings undated (Box 23)
      - Miscellanea (Box 23)
    - College league papers
      - General (Box 23)
      - Michigan State University 1947 (Box 23)
      - University of Michigan
        - By-laws undated (Box 23)
        - Annual reports 1952-1953 (Box 23)
        - Correspondence 1954 (Box 23)
        - Minutes 1952 (Box 23)
      - Wayne State University
        - Annual reports 1949-1953 (Box 23)
        - Correspondence 1949-1956 (Box 23)
        - Newspaper clippings 1951 (Box 23)
- Officers Files
  - Charlotte Copp Papers
    - Annual Reports
      - Local Leagues 1973, 1977, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - National Board Reports 1974-1978 (Box 24)
    - Conferences
      - Midwest Conference (Box 24)
      - Seminar (Box 24)
    - Courts
      - General, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Selection of Judges, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Human Resources
      - Education
        - Busing, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Coalition for Financing Equitable Education (Box 24)
        - 1969-1974 (Box 24)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - Legislation 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Housing
      - Conference 1974 (Box 24)
      - General (Box 24)
      - Metro Housing Committee 1973 (Box 24)
      - Metro Study Committee 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Social Services
      - General 1969-1975, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Welfare
      - Women's Issues (Box 25)
      - ERA (Box 25)
      - Houston Conference (Box 25)
      - International Women's Year and Focus: Michigan Women (Box 25)
      - Women-in-Politics Seminar (Box 25)
      - General (Box 25)
    - International Relations
      - China (Box 25)
      - Development and Trade (Box 25)
      - United Nations (Box 25)
    - Legislation
      - State
        - Legislative Action (notebooks)
          - 1969-1974 (Box 25)
          - 1974-1978 (Box 25)
        - "Legislative News," 1972-1973 (newsletter) (Box 25)
        - Local Program Listings 1967-1974 (Box 25)
      - National
        - "Report From the Hill"
          - 1972-1975 (Box 26)
          - 1976-1978 (Box 26)
    - National Conventions
      - 1972 (Box 26)
      - 1974 (Box 26)
      - 1976 (Box 26)
    - National Councils
      - 1971 (Box 26)
      - 1973 (Box 26)
      - 1975 (Box 26)
      - 1977 (Box 26)
    - Natural Resources
      - Environmental Quality
        - Air (Box 26)
        - Energy 1970-1976 (Box 26)
        - Energy Educating Projects, Phase I and II (Box 26)
        - Energy-Thermal (Box 26)
        - Lake Erie Basin Group (Box 26)
        - Lake Michigan, 3 folders (Box 26)
        - Lake Superior (Box 26)
        - National Testimony (Box 26)
        - Pesticides (Box 26)
        - Saginaw River Basin (Box 26)
        - Solid Waste-Bottle Bill Campaign 1975-1976 (Box 26)
        - Water Quality, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Land Use
        - Coastal Zone Management Project 1977-1978 (Box 27)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Representative Government
      - District of Columbia, 4 folders (Box 27)
      - Financing Government Services (Box 27)
      - Local Government (Box 27)
      - Taxation Assessment Practices Study 1973 (Box 27)
    - State Councils
      - 1968 (Box 27)
      - 1970 (Box 27)
      - 1972 (Box 27)
      - 1974 (Box 27)
      - 1976 (Box 27)
      - 1978 (Box 27)
    - Taxation
      - 1967-1976 (Box 27)
      - Citizens Lobby (Box 27)
    - "Time for Action" 1965-1975, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Workshops
      - 1961-1963 (Box 27)
      - 1964-1969 (Box 27)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 27)
      - 1978 (Box 27)
    - Voters
      - Michigan (Box 27)
      - "The National Voter," 1975-1978 (Box 27)
    - Local League Reports
      - Alpena County (Box 28)
      - Ann Arbor (Box 28)
      - Battle Creek (Box 28)
      - Bay County (Box 28)
      - Cadillac (Box 28)
      - Copper Country (Houghton) (Box 28)
      - Dearborn (Box 28)
      - Delta County (Box 28)
      - Detroit (Box 28)
      - Detroit Metropolitan Area (Box 28)
      - Down River Wayne County (Box 28)
      - Eastern Ottawa County (Box 28)
      - Flint (Box 28)
      - Grand Haven-Spring Lake-Ferryburg Area (Box 28)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 28)
      - Grand Traverse Area (Box 28)
      - Gratiot County (Box 28)
      - Grosse Pointe (Box 28)
      - Holland Area (Box 28)
      - Jackson County (Box 28)
      - Kalamazoo Area (Box 28)
      - Livingston County (Box 28)
      - Lansing Area (Box 28)
      - Livonia (Box 28)
      - Manistee County (Box 28)
      - Marquette County (Box 28)
      - Midland Area (Box 28)
      - Monroe County (Box 28)
      - Mount Clemens-Clinton Area (Box 28)
      - Mount Pleasant Area (Box 28)
      - Muskegon Area (Box 28)
      - Niles-Buchanan Area (Box 28)
      - Northville-Plymouth Area (Box 28)
      - Petoskey (Box 28)
      - Port Huron (Box 28)
      - Rochester (Box 29)
      - Royal Oak (Box 29)
      - Saginaw (Box 29)
      - Saginaw County (Box 29)
      - Sault Sainte Marie Area, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Southfield-Lathrop Village (Box 29)
      - Troy (Box 29)
      - Warren (Box 29)
      - West Bloomfield-Farmington (Box 29)
      - West Oakland County (Box 29)
  - Katherine Cushman Papers
    - Office Files
      - Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box 29)
      - Budgets and Treasurers' Reports (State) 1979 (Box 29)
      - Correspondence 1979-1981 (Box 29)
      - Council of Organizations and Others for Education about Parochiaid (CAP) 1978-1980 (Box 29)
      - "Legislative News," 1977-1978 (Box 29)
      - Michigan Education Forum Minutes March 1978-April 1980 (Box 29)
      - Research, Evaluation, and Assessment Service Advisory Council (Box 29)
      - State Board Reports 1978-1979 (Box 29)
      - "Time for Action," 1967-1970 (Box 29)
    - Issue Files
      - Administration 1979-1980 (Box 29)
      - Legislative Programs 1973-1978 (Box 29)
      - Natural Resources 1973-1980 (Box 29)
      - School Financing 1973-1978 (Box 29)
      - Voter Services
        - Correspondence 1970-1977 (Box 29)
        - Printed Material (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Budget Committee 1974-1977 (Box 30)
      - Charlotte Copp Tribute (Box 30)
      - ERA (Box 30)
      - Field Service Correspondence 1967-1977 (Box 30)
      - Field Service Reports
        - 1968-1974 (Box 30)
        - 1978-1981 (Box 30)
      - Finance Advisory Board (Box 30)
      - Juvenile Justice-Children's Services (Box 30)
      - Legislative Interviews (Box 30)
      - Local and State Officers 1975-1979 (Box 30)
      - National Action Alerts 1977-1979 (Box 30)
      - National Convention 1978 (Box 30)
      - National Program 1973 (Box 30)
      - Political Issues (Box 30)
      - State Program and Index 1977-1979 (Box 30)
      - "The State We're In" (Box 30)
    - Later files
      - Constitutional Convention
        - Resource Materials 1961 (Box 30)
        - Convention Reports 1961-1962 (Box 30)
        - Campaign for New Constitution 1962-1963 (Box 30)
      - Legislative Contracts
        - American Association of University Professors/Association of Michigan Collegiate Faculties 1975-1977 (Box 30)
        - Bureau of National Affairs/Legislex 1977-1978 (Box 30)
        - Michigan occupational Education Association 1975-1977 (Box 30)
        - Michigan Reading Association 1975-1977 (Box 30)
        - Michigan School Social Workers Association 1976 (Box 30)
        - Miscellaneous Contract Inquiries 1975-1978 (Box 30)
  - Priscilla Chave files
    - Subject files (Box 31)
  - Judith Rose files
    - State Board and convention files 1978-1995 (Box 38)
- Later initiatives
  - Legislative Action 1987 (Box 37)
  - Funding of Public Libraries 1988 (Box 37)
  - Prison study 1987-1990, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Groundwater Education in Michigan (GEM) 1989-1990, 22 folders (Box 37)
  - Published material (Box 37)